baopals.com 2018-03-09

# Privacy Policy - Baopals

### Section 1 – What do we do with your information?

When you purchase something from our website, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us (e.g. name, address and email address).

When you browse our site, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (ip) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system. This data is not linked to your personal information.

Email marketing: From time to time, at our discretion, we may send you emails about our platform, new products and promotional materials (such as coupons).

### Section 2 – Consent

How do you get my consent?

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

How do I withdraw my consent?

If, after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent at anytime by contacting us at [support@baopals.com](mailto:support@baopals.com).

**Juvenile Protection**

This website is intended for users ages 13 and older. Accordingly, we will not knowingly collect or use any personal information from children that we know to be under the age of 13. In addition, we will delete any information in our database that we know originates from a child under the age of 13. Prospective users between the ages of 13 and 17 can only use our services under their parents' or legal guardian's supervision. If you are between the ages of 13 and 17, you, your parent, or your legal guardian may request that we delete any of your personal information in our database and/or opt-out from receiving communications from us.

### Section 3 – Disclosure

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our terms of service.

### Section 4 – Payment

Payment processing for Baopals orders is handled by third-party payment gateways Asiapay and Ping++. It is encrypted through the payment card industry data security standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.

All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the pci security standards council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover.

Pci-dss requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our platform and its service providers.

For more insight, you may find Asiapay’s privacy statement [here](http://www.asiapay.com/privacy.html).

### Section 5 – Third-Party Services

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers. In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located in a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.

Once you leave our website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this privacy policy or our website’s terms of service.

Links: when you click on links on our platform, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

### Section 6 – Security

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

### Section 7 – Age of Consent

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

### Section 8 – Changes to This Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time without notice, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website.

If our platform is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

### Questions and Contact Information

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our privacy compliance officer at support@baopals.com.

#### Last Updated June 8, 2016
